JEREMY WALKER

Bozeman, MT 59715 | jeremycalewalker@gmail.com

Profile Summary

Developer with a background in marketing where I have worked in web building and SEO/analytics. Experience in working on and managing a team. Skilled in building relationships with clients and vendors to help oversee projects from start to finish.

Experience

Zoot Enterprises

Solutions Developer | September 2021 – Now

- ✓ Developing a web platform for a pharmaceutical company.
- √ Tech stack: Node.js, React, HTML, XML, CSS, JavaScript, mySQL, Linux/PuTTY
- ✓ Troubleshoot existing platforms, examine logs, solve any defects that are found/reported and consistently improve UX.
- ✓ Use JIRA and Confluence for daily tasks, to track the progress of development and deadlines, and collaborate with my team.

JT's Hard Gum

Front-End Developer/Co-founder | January 2019 - October 2021

- √ Started a jaw strengthening gum company.
- ✓ Designed, developed and launched an e-commerce platform.
- √ Tech stack: Node.js, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, SEO, Wordpress, Google Analytics
- ✓ Arranged sales channels on Amazon, and coordinated wholesale orders.
- ✓ Established and maintained relationships with influencers who promoted the brand.

Yellowstone Club

Estate Manager | August 2020 - September 2021

- √ Managed a portfolio of 13 homes, totaling \$130 million in equity.
- ✓ Maintained a spreadsheet of each home's scheduled, pending, approved and completed projects.
- ✓ Duties included establishing and maintaining relationships with homeowners, vendors, and contractors and keeping each home in perfect working order.

SW Montana Mountain Bike Association

Marketing Manager | August 2018 - August 2020

- √ Built an Integrated Marketing Communications plan for the non-profit.
- √ Tech Stack: HTML5, CSS3, SEO, Google analytics
- √ Facilitated building a marketing budget.

Education

Bachelor of Science - Marketing

Montana State University, Bozeman | August 2016 - May 2020

Certificates in Full-Stack Web Development

Free Code Camp | December 2018 – March 2019

√ 300+ hours of intensive project-based training with a focus on React, Node.js, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, & most prominent libraries, frameworks, tools.

SKILLS

Reac

Node.is

HTML/HTML5

XM

CSS/CSS3

JavaScript (1997)

iQuery

MvSOI

Responsive Design

Wordpress

TOOLKIT

Git/GitHub

Google Analytics

Google Tag Manage

Adobe Creative Suite

JIRA/Confluence

Linux/PuTTY